question_data = [{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                  "question": "The song &quot;Stronger Than You&quot; is a single by Estelle, who played Garnet in Steven Universe.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                  "question": "Muse is a British (English) rock band", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                  "question": "Lead Singer Rivers Cuomo of American rock band Weezer attended Harvard.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                  "question": "Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                  "question": "The music group Daft Punk got their name from a negative review they recieved.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                  "question": "Scatman John&#039;s real name was John Paul Larkin.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                  "question": "American rapper Dr. Dre actually has a Ph.D. doctorate.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                  "question": "Daft Punk originated in France.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                  "question": "The 2011 movie &quot;The Adventures of Tintin&quot; was directed by Steven Spielberg.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                  "question": "The alternative rock band, They Might Be Giants, released their album &#039;Flood&#039; in 1990. ",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
